http://www.addictfantasysports.com/privacypolicy.php

About   Add a Site
AllTeacherWebsites.com respects your privacy.
Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of AllTeacherWebsites.com.
Credit card details
AllTeacherWebsites.com will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on AllTeacherWebsites.com.
External Sites
AllTeacherWebsites.com is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.
Log Files
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in
log files.  The information in the log files include your IP (internet
protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or
Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet
Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you
visited throughout our site.
Cookies and Web Beacons
A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows AllTeacherWebsites.com to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and AllTeacherWebsites.com does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeed providers and advertising firms.
We use third party advertisements on AllTeacherWebsites.com to support our
site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and
web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these
advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program)
information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used
to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash
installed.  These companies may use information
about your visits to this and other
websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of
interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice
and to know your choices about not having this information used by
these companies, you can read more about it and/or opt out here.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or
third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing
preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However,
this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as
other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services
or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet
If you post a comment in our forum on the site,
you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you
submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of those
forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not
responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to
submit in this forum. We reserve the right to remove any offensive or
personally identifiable information that is posted.
While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to AllTeacherWebsites.com and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through AllTeacherWebsites.com have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.
If you post a comment in our forum on the site,
you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you
submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of those
forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not
responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to
submit in this forum. We reserve the right to remove any offensive or
personally identifiable information that is posted.
Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.
For any other information email the webmaster spamhut [at] gmail [dot] com.
© 2007-2011 JensenWeb, LLC.
All Rights Reserved. Privacy Policy
